arriving at Antarctic
Peninsula why would you live someplace
with snow year
round snow is so
beautiful until it stepped upon the
Antarctic
pinula is it snowing I really love it
when it snows the snow here is quite
mild compared to the ice caps back home
such a tragedy what happened here poor
Dr Joe remember May they wouldn't want
you to be sad I heard someone climbed
over Tana without
ropes tauras would have been so jealous
this is a far cry from my home need a
good fight to warm me up that was just a
warmup there better be no Penguins on
this base I like it here perhaps I will
stay so much D this Eco watch point I
get the Shivers just thinking about it h
it's even colder in Siberia
welcome to Blizzard world I'm definitely
too old for a trip to the amusement park
oh can we ride the hell scream over here
please please please please please now
traveling to
Busan Reinhardt why don't you give it a
try if they destroy any of my favorite
mats I'm coming for them it's nice being
on home turf each Gan attack strengthens
The Defenders as a furnace hardens Steel
I heard their fish cakes here are famous
wish one of those big underwater robots
would attack I don't need a Mech to
fight them a guitar isn't the only thing
I shred you're lucky I don't rip off
your head I know sacrifice and I know
pain I forgot the words again uh time
for the
[Applause]
Reckoning did I do that right how am I
supposed to sing if I do not know the
word
what's happening
bu I can't hear you sorry sorry I'm so
sorry ah come on Snowball Dance with
me I love this
song I cannot believe I am being
subjected to this
cacophony and they say my actions are
unethical no I am not enjoying this fly
fools get with the times prepare
yourselves for Farah's Rhymes I am going
to shoot you down Farah reporting coming
to town I'm the best when push come to
shove direct complaints to my metal
glove here comes the moment that you all
love Justice Reigns from above lyrical
superiority achieved pop it lock it
Mercy in my pocket even get can't seem
to block
it get down with Sigma
tonight like a stro
raffle
ooh ooh
yeah come on now oh yeah baby come
on I wonder what the landlord's password
is so simple let's change that for you
let's order some pizza for the
neighborhood and pay their rent huh and
all their dead the network security here
is so soft and cute it's like hacking a
marshmallow The Raid leader in the
gaming Cafe upstairs is so rude oh no
his computer crashed this song library
is too small no problem I'll add some
chip Tunes why would I sing this little
song when I can make the world sing for
me everything by my design drawing
triangles tracing lines it's wise to
disrespect such an efficient architect
hopefully by now you see the result of
My reality everything according to plan
move your feet move your
hands their actions convey futility
their minds are close to possibility but
still order wins the
day turrets here turrets there placing
turrets everywhere my teleporter is
online perhaps it's best if you resign
arriving at Shadow gear such poor
manners for a guest this is private
property welcome to Circuit Royale I
love these cars wonder if they let me
drive one when are they going to make a
Supercar my size I love car races high
octane burning rubber um The Thrill of
the chase oh pedal to the medal
H I want a car this city is
dazzling and far more lavish than I can
handle I remember we had Burns here
under deep cover for about 6 years she
got so good at cards she quit OverWatch
and played fulltime I remember we were
looking into Corsini
SPC let's just say they're involved with
more than Ellie say and fancy cars
anyone want drinks they're on Max's tab
rambling is a n Only a Fool Believes In
luck maximillian's tastes are quite
extravagant high concentrations of
valuable items found Omega priority
message sent to read it arriving at
coloso I hear you can smuggle just about
anything through those skyways let's
visit the ctin chapel after this I want
to get a closer look at that ceiling
sitting in cafes all day drinking good
espresso eating pasta with eight
syllable names
not a bad way to live no one expected
the Roman Empire to
fall perhaps that is why it did I
understand the path that Caesar took but
more than that I understand his fall I
don't see what's so fancy about Rome
hardly any scrap Apes at all have you
tried the coffee here it'll make your
eyes vibrate out of your skull I played
the sickest concert here Coliseum hasn't
been that pack since Spartacus Andy
kower EST nir senica said that the cause
of fear is
ignorance if only anyone had listened I
remember we were looking into Corsini
SPC let's just say they're involved with
more than Elis and fancy cars is tread
weather ever going to patch the control
override on these damn things I admire
the hardlight sculptures in this city
there are wonderful artists here the
damn Tower I don't care if tourists like
it it's falling over and it needs to be
fixed When in Rome do as the Romans do
and I sure hope the Romans like studying
columns the die has been cast I know
Rome wasn't built in a day but we don't
have that kind of time I came I saw I
conquered classical archaeology my
favorite note to self design sweet Roman
gladiator armor with scary
grapple traveling to
Dorado thank goodness my parachutes
deploy explo
properly onion
cilantro yeah remind me to visit Mita
while I'm in Mexico I got to show her
pictures from my last dig traveling to
ional at times I can't almost hear the
voices of those who lost their lives
here I hope those who died defending
this place have found peace they say a
bansi haunts these
grounds but those are just fairy tales
poor Reinhardt
what he must have seen here I don't want
to stick around here something in the
air makes my eyes water oh this place
gives me the heie jeebies check out the
stratification in this Castle stonework
looks like a lot of groups have called
this place home every site tells a
story not always happy ones medieval
archaeology my favorite I've got the hee
chibies good thing I packed the Volo
welcome to ish pansa
assassins tracked me down here once they
regretted it briefly Portugal why on
Earth are we in Portugal I keep meaning
to visit the Martin's museum while I'm
here I love how this town honors them
yet another stretch of cloudless skies
and idyllic ocean
views
wonderful is tread weather ever going to
patch the control override on these damn
things I like being near the ocean it
reminds me of where I was was born
traveling to hanamura I should really
visit ASA
Sensei but I already know what she's
going to say I should check in on Mr
Yoshida while I'm here and maybe get
some sweets for aari the Hashimoto rule
this town with fear it's time we give
them something to be afraid of let me
show you
around arriving at
hanoka it is not my duty to face the
Hashimoto yet
I cannot bear to walk away what has
become of my home I remember this place
this is where I learned not to drink soy
sauce I should check in on Mr Yoshida
while I'm here and maybe get some sweets
for aari the Hashimoto rule this town
with fear it's time we give them
something to be afraid of let me show
you
around traveling to Havana I hate to
work on vacation let's sneak in a trip
to the beach after the
I won't tell if you don't weather report
a storm is rising these conditions are
not optimal for
experimentation but they are optimal for
a tan Emme always said he'd retire here
wonder where he ended up you guys ever
drink this Dono G the old stuff was way
better I like being near the ocean it
reminds me of where I was
born Welcome to
Hollywood h how far is it to
Malibu the paparazzi better not get in
my way ooh I'd like to see my Name In
Lights one day a cowboy with six
guns oh Father will love this think
we'll see AI skyus I I love everything
he's in though he does always make me
cry I refuse to die on a movie set I
should make movies Ching money you know
they tried to make a movie about the
founding of OverWatch
total flop the guy who played me what an
amateur a these horror faks can't
believe they're making another rise of
the
znic wait in 5D I cannot imagine living
here movie stars or no I've got the heie
chibies good thing I packed the Volo
traveling to Horizon Luna Colony space
really puts the world in A New
Perspective my entire Realm in plain
view Blues greens yellows oh Earth's
colors are so
beautiful so much to heal hey look you
could see the super Coral from here
makes you feel really
small okay let's go break some beers our
world is worth fighting for a dreamer is
one who can only find his way by
Moonlight and his punishment is that he
sees the dawn before the rest of the
world we are all in the gutter but some
of us are looking at the stars the views
not bad by looking far out into space we
are also looking far back into time back
toward the Horizon of the universe the
stars are like the trees in the forest
alive and breathing and they're watching
us Beyond the Edge of the World there's
a space where emptiness and substance
neatly overlap where past and future
form a continuous endless loop and
hovering about there are signs no one
has ever read chords no one has ever
heard wow I need to get one of these
that's something you don't see every day
think about all that's happened down
there that's
home that's us on it everyone you love
everyone you know everyone you ever
heard of every human being whoever was
lived out their lives the aggregate of
our joy and suffering every Hunter and
forager every hero and coward every
Creator and destroyer of
civilization every King and peasant
every young couple in love every mother
and father hopeful child inventor and
Explorer and every saint and sinner in
history lived there the first day or so
we all pointed to our countries the
third or fourth day we were pointing to
our
continents by the fifth day we were
aware of only one Earth to see the Earth
as it truly is small and blue and
beautiful in that Eternal silence where
it floats is to see ourselves as Riders
on the earth together Brothers on that
bright loveliness in the Eternal cold
brothers who know now they are truly
Brothers now arriving at
ilos I hate to work on vacation let's
hurry this along there's a beaching
treat with my name on it I've always
been a good shot lucky shot I wouldn't
mind stealing a spaceship you hear what
they make satellites out of these days
we used to come here on vacation let me
know if you need any dire
Bingo let's sneak in a trip to the beach
after this I won't tell if you don't
boom shakalaka she's on fire simple
geometry 0.4 seconds to go there's the
buzzer and he scores he's done it boom
shaka
laka buckets I call that a 300,000
pointer there is water everywhere is
that not a safety hazard go home run
Lucio's football lessons were very
helpful touchdown like it's hard what'
you expect you're up
faran simple geometry like threading a
needle oh from downtown YY I got it
piece of cake I do have a bit of
experience after all yet another stretch
of cloudless skies and idilic ocean
views
wonderful saving highlight was the sun
in your eyes clean shot easy ho in one H
terrible vacation Bingo these conditions
are not optimal for
experimentation but they are optimal for
a tan what is gravity to an expert I
really need to come here off the clock
been dying to try the octopus game over
want to see me run around the sh want to
see me do it again classical archaeology
my favorite whatever Talon's looking for
I won't let it fall into their hands
I've got my eye on you Talon Boos touch
anything and you'll taste this drill I
hear the sticks is lovely this time of
year smooth as silk oh yeah I like being
near the ocean it reminds me of where I
was born beginner's luck welcome to
junka
town got dust stuck in my teeth this
place confuses me if it is so hostile to
life why does everyone not leave this is
a silly place a less honorable place is
difficult to Imagine ah how I've missed
the smell of our plutonium Springs this
city is mine and it's staying mine take
me down to junker town where the grass
is brown and the sky is brown remember
the plan HomeField Advantage you know
Queen couldn't have done better herself
payloads moving oh the Queen's going to
love this
got to stop in and see no eyes Tad
though he never sees me m smell that I
think Outback bill is working up a Bobby
the scenery here reminds me of home
though the smell is quite different do
not worry I am an expert at navigating
dust storms it is time someone cleaned
up this Lawless Wasteland these junkers
do not care for
BS the sentiment is mutual back again
huh I'm in junker town with a bunch of
junkers not sure how today could get any
worse I wish I could disable my sense of
smell H better keep an eye on the omnium
radiation levels I hear they call him
the Champ here and to think he used to
sleep inside my pillow do not kick rocks
into hamster's house welcome to the
hamster playground how can anyone stand
to live here usus strange as it seems I
believe this place may have something to
teach us now traveling to kazaka I
should check in on Mr Yoshida while I'm
here and maybe get some sweets for aari
the Hashimoto rule this town with fear
it's time we give them something to be
afraid of let me show you around kazaka
is under my protection no one's taking
my home from me now entering King's Row
talk can jump over Big Ben no problem
this is London huh I've seen fancier I
wouldn't change a thing we did here I
can't believe I fell for all that anti-
omnic clap trap how dare you come back
here now arriving at y Jang Tower I've
always been a good shot lucky shot I
wouldn't mind stealing a spaceship you
hear what they make satellites out of
these days Bingo boom shaka laka she is
on fire luchang understands an important
fact as long as we are Shackled to a
single planet we are vulnerable I would
love to go to the night market after
this simple geometry 0.4 seconds to go
there's the buzzer and he scores he's
done it boom shaka
laka buckets I call that a 300,000
pointer go home
run l luo's football lessons were very
helpful touchdown I cannot help but
wonder how our base lost contact with L
Chang like it's hard what' you expect
you're up
faran simple geometry like threading a
needle oh from downtown hey I got it my
friend J worked here she and I had a lot
of fun in grad school maybe too much who
would have thought that J would end up
on Mars piece of cake I do have a bit of
experience after all saving highlight
clean shot easy you think luchang
Interstellar is
clean nobody's clean hold in one H Bingo
what is gravity to an expert game over
want to see me run around the shov want
to see me do it again smooth as silk oh
yeah beginner's luck now entering
Midtown this City's louder than a field
of Montana grasshoppers you know the
ones as big as your thumb why stop it
making it here I'm thinking more Global
the transit system here is fascinating
so much automation so many
destinations I hope to study it someday
the city that never sleeps that sounds
like me this city is always so noisy why
was traffic even invented father said
there is authentic Vietnamese food in in
big cities what should I try first the
pizza here doesn't even come with
ketchup it's outrageous these tiny
streets can't cage me in New York New
York a summer smell you'll never forget
if we can make it here we can make it
anywhere I tend to avoid places this
crowded they definitely know basketball
here even the teenagers will break your
ankles in a pickup game the NTI here is
said to be unlike anywhere in the world
huh
I would like to leave before the sun
goes down these New Yorkers could stand
to learn some manners no city in the
world can compare to Utopia all these
skyscrapers just hurt my neck broken
safety compliances everywhere City of
Lights I prefer the Northern Lights New
York's Chief engineering advisor has
returned now this is what proper
engineering does for a city the Big
Apple someone take my picture this city
is filthy overrun by rats and the people
are terribly rude nothing like Paris I
bet the view at the top of the Empire
State Building is great the hamster
intends to spin around the skyscraper
you cannot stop him I won Gold in the
summer games here had a cold and a torn
trapezius a refreshing challenge if a
city never sleeps how can it dream
traveling to Nepal I've always been a
good shot lucky sh I wouldn't mind
stealing a spaceship you hear what they
make satellites out of these days why
would you live someplace with snow year
round I'm surprised Papas come around on
omnic usually it doesn't change his mind
about anything Bingo boom shakalaka
she's on fire Dr Lea told me of her
journey
here it is strange to see it with my own
eyes this should be a place of
reflection and
learning it SS me that it is in danger
snow is so
beautiful until it stepped upon simple
geometry is it snowing I really love it
when it snows 0.4 seconds to go there's
the buzzer and he scores he's done it
boom shaka
laka buckets I call that a 300,000
pointer the snow here is quite mild
compared to the ice caps back home go
home run
Lucio's football lessons were very
helpful touchdown like it's hard what'
you expect you're up
faran simple geometry I like this place
it's contemplative like threading a
needle the home of the iris so inspiring
to be in the presence of a force that
defines the limits of our understanding
oh from downtown hey I got it piece of
cake I do have a bit of experience after
all H being is born of science seeking
answers in faith saving highlight clean
shot easy ho in one H
Bingo H strange fluctuations emanate
through this space what is gravity to an
expert game over I'm a little
embarrassed of some of the things I said
here but I'm doing my best to learn want
to see me run around the shuttle want to
see me do it again this is where Aurora
changed the world forever I am going to
freak out smooth as silk oh yeah it's
even colder in Siberia beginners luck
perhaps they believe we will not defend
this place but if all the rest of the
world were to fall this would be the
stand I chose to make there is little so
renewing as a breath of Mountain Air or
so I have been told welcome to New young
City this is a silly place a less
honorable place is difficult to Imagine
ah how I've missed the smell of our
plutonium Springs this city is mine and
it's staying mine better find my
subjects up to no good they always get
soft when I'm not around yeah this is my
city don't you dare put a scratch on it
got to stop in and see no eyes Tad
though he never sees me hey M smell that
I think Outback bill is working up a
Bobby it is time someone cleaned up this
Lawless Wasteland these junkers do not
care for
Bots the sentiment is mutual H better
keep an eye on the omnium radiation
levels I hear they call him the Champ
here and to think he used to sleep
inside my pillow do not kick rocks in
the hamster's house welcome to the
hamster playground how can anyone stand
to live here usus strange as it seems I
believe this place may have something to
teach us traveling to new Queen Street
snow is so
beautiful until it stepped upon is it
snowing I really love it when it snows
father said there is authentic
Vietnamese food in big cities what
should I try first I live here so don't
blow up anything you don't have to my
home and native land the true north
strong and free surprised everyone got
here on time the 401 was backed up like
crazy as usual is tread weather ever
going to patch the control override on
these damn things sometimes I miss
Canada but the world's not going to
explore itself hamster has detected
pancakes bring pancakes to the hamster
or the hamster will locate
pancakes traveling to numani these
people moved past the crisis so quickly
I envy that so this is where doomfist is
from I hope he's not in town if only you
could see me now ad Yi just as sheep
must have a Shepherd numani must have me
you say they have advanced robotics here
have they built anyone like me it's so
hot ah I forgot my summer clothes again
if he was right the junis have taken GR
great care of our home many have tried
to destroy this city but Nani will
always hold strong Mo you are not
welcome in my domain you will never take
our city now this is a city that
understands engineering and that child
genius wo a future Ironclad no doubt
welcome to Oasis Papa said to deliver my
manuscript in person but I'd be a little
embarrassed
these Oasis fools have got to learn they
can keep people down
forever tore this place up the pursuit
of knowledge
Unshackled tempting but so
dangerous Fain city of unfettered
scientists yeah until they call Helix in
tears at 2: in the morning because the
wolfbats escaped again I hate this place
ah
Oasis I miss miss the quiet confines of
a laboratory might be hypocritical of me
but I think there are some parts of
science humans weren't meant to
explore now traveling to parisu I hate
to work on vacation when was my last
trip to Copa
Cabana too long ago now this is one
place that knows how to throw a party
let's sneak in a trip to the beach after
this I won't tell if you don't so this
is where Lucio grew up these conditions
are not optimal for
experimentation but they are optimal for
a tan vish's actions here were
disappointing I still need answers for
them Welcome to Rio ladies and gentlemen
welcome to Paris the city of
love weather report Killer Robots wait
that can be right I would love to learn
French one day welcome to
Rialto Antonio was a fool I remember
this
place Sumptuous Italian vacation begins
now there is water everywhere is that
not a safety hazard this city brings
back memories what news on the
Realto sorry not damn Tower I don't care
if tourists like it it's falling over
and it needs to be fixed traveling to
Route
66 this place just ain't the same since
that son of a gun ran away with my bike
that bridge collapsed from a little
explosion seems like bad engineering to
me a mea road trip would be Tor the fun
it's a completely different view outside
the crate do not worry I am an expert at
navigating dust storms these are the
first cacti I've seen that weren't dying
on somebody's window sill it's so hot ah
I forgot my summer clothes again
yeah it's a dry heat my West is Wilder
this part of the country is so beautiful
reminds me of road trips when I was a
kid different world and we'll never get
it
back welcome to runas sappi everyone
keeps asking me when I will
return but how can I after everything
that's happened I hate being
here it feels feels like they're
watching me I wish I could be anywhere
but
here at least I can visit Juno let's
just get this over with so we can leave
why did it have to be
here Pai Peruvian archaeology my
favorite if I look really hard I bet I
could see the noscal lines from here
welcome to samua that's always been a
good shot lucky shot Bingo boom shaka
laka she's on fire simple geometry 0.4
seconds to go there's the buzzer Andy
scores he's done it boom shaka
laka buckets I call that a 300,000
pointer go home
run Lucio's football lessons were very
helpful touchdown like it's hard what'
you expect you're up
faran simple geometry like threading a
needle oh from
downtown miss that smell my old stomping
grounds not the brag but I'm kind of a
big thing around these parts this is
home turf Bud oh that's the island
welcome YY I got it piece of cake I do
have a bit of experience after all yet
another stretch of cloudless skies and
idyllic ocean
views
wonderful waving highlight clean shot
easy hole in one H let's win quickly I
want to hit the beach bingo least it's
nice here what is gravity to an expert
game over smooth as silk oh yeah
beginner's luck now arriving at the
shambali monastery I'm sensing a strange
energy here it
feels pure snow
is so
beautiful until it stepped upon is it
snowing I really love it when it snows
the snow here is quite mild compared to
the ice caps back home the home of the
iris so inspiring to be in the presence
of a force that defines the limits of
our understanding H beings born of
science seeking answers in Faith H
strange fluctuations emanate through
this space this is where Aurora changed
the world forever
I am going to freak out perhaps they
believe we will not defend this place
but if all the rest of the world were to
fall this would be the stand I chose to
make there is little so renewing as a
breath of Mountain Air or so I have been
told now entering the Temple of Anubis
if Anubis were ever to rise again I hope
I would remember who I am just as a is
opened the gates of death I will exhaust
myself to keep them shut egyptology my
favorite just look at the array of
pristine late Kingdom hieroglyphics here
o I think this one is a curse hope your
heart's not heavy approaching the Throne
of Anubis Anubis is an interesting case
to think a single program could have
such a profound effect on the world if
AIS were ever to rise again
I hope I would remember who I am just as
Anubis opened the gates of death I will
exhaust myself to keep them shut can't
believe Anubis is just here after all
the pain it caused hology my favorite
just look at the array of pristine late
Kingdom hieroglyphics here o I think
this one is a curse hope your heart's
not heavy the AI that caused the crisis
is quarantined in this Temple so uh
let's be careful huh traveling to
volskaya Industries snow is so beautiful
until it stepped upon arriving at watch
Point Gibralter I wouldn't mind stealing
a spaceship you hear what they make
satellites out of these days so many
memories Gibralter is bigger than they
remember or maybe it's just that I've
never seen it so empty OverWatch
keepers of the status quo I am proud to
be here I should have burned jalter to
the
ground maybe I still can looks like
Gibralter is back online with lots of
new Intel to share sometimes I wish
OverWatch would come back just so I
could get some new Intel from this Ghost
Town let's make this quick I have peanut
butter banana bread in the oven